let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "S – 1: The square root of certain decimals are obtained by first changing the decimals into fractions with perfect squares as their numerators and denominators.  S - 2 : (26.1)^2 lies between 400 and 900.",
        answer: "Both Statement-1 and Statement-2 are true",
        options: [
          "S-1 is true but S-2 is false.",
          "S-1 is false but S-2 is true.",
          "Both Statement-1 and Statement-2 are false.",
          "Both Statement-1 and Statement-2 are true"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Thor is thinking of two numbers. Their greatest common factor is 6. Their least common multiple is 36. One of the numbers is 12. What is the other number",
        answer: "18",
        options: [
          "18",
          "16",
          "6",
          "24"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Three numbers are in the ratio of 2:3:4 . The sum of their cubes is 33957. Find the largest number.",
        answer: "28",
        options: [
          "28",
          "21",
          "32",
          "14"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Find the value of x: (9x+7)/2 – [x-(x-2)/7]=36",
        answer: "9",
        options: [
          "18",
          "27",
          "9",
          "14"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Three numbers are in the ratio of 4:3:2. The sum of their cubes is 21384. The smallest number is ___.",
        answer: "12",
        options: [
          "15",
          "6",
          "10",
          "12"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 6,
        question: "The value of sixth root of (91125/216)^2 is ____",
        answer: "7.5",
        options: [
          "4",
          "2.5",
          "7.5",
          "8.5"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 7,
        question: "The cube of a number x is four times of x then find x. (x not equals to 0 and -2).",
        answer: "2",
        options: [
          "1",
          "2",
          "0",
          "4"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 8,
        question: "In five digit number 13ab4, a is the greatest single digit perfect cube and a is greater 4 times of b, then find the number.",
        answer: "13824",
        options: [
          "13824",
          "13848",
          "13825",
          "13820"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 9,
        question: "y% of 50 + 5% of 10 = 15, then y = ____.",
        answer: "29",
        options: [
          "22",
          "29",
          "21",
          "30"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Sum of money is borrowed and paid back by Hulk in two annual installments of $882 each allowing 5% compound interest. The sum borrowed was ____ $.",
        answer: "1640",
        options: [
          "1620",
          "1690",
          "1660",
          "1640"
        ]
      },

];